<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NaviBlind Two</string>
    <string name="floor_plan">Floor Plan</string>
    <string name="debug">Launch Debug</string>
    <string name="test_speech">Test Speech</string>


    <string name="empty"></string>

    <string name="no_service">Please wait...service not ready.</string>

    <string name="try_again">Please try again...</string>

    <string name="welcome">Welcome to the Department of Computer Science. You are now
                on the second floor of the extension building.For room number two six
                seven, walk to your right towards the main door, this is normally open
                but please exercise caution.</string>

    <string name="welcome_two">Welcome to the Department of Computer Science.
                You are now on the second floor of the extension building.
                This application will guide you to room number two six seven.
                When ready to start, wait for the notification alert and say "I am ready to start".</string>

    <string name="main_door">Have you gone through the main fire exit door in front of you?
                Please say Yes when ready.</string>

    <string name="after_main_door">Keep walking forward for about ten (10) steps. Then turn
                cautiously to the right and take the sub-level stairways containing four steps
                down towards the main corridor.</string>

    <string name="four_steps">Can you confirm the presence of the four step sub-level stairway
                in front of you? Please say Yes when ready.</string>

    <string name="narrow_corridor">Keep walking forward and take the four step sub-level stairway
                down to the main corridor. This corridor is narrow and long, keep walking forward
                for about twenty (20) steps. At the end of this corridor take the sub-level
                stairways containing two steps up and turn right towards room two six seven (267).
                </string>

    <string name="two_steps">Can you confirm the presence of the two step sub-level stairway in
                front of you? Please say Yes when ready.</string>

    <string name="at_two_steps">Take the sub-level stairways containing two steps up and turn right
                towards room two six seven (267). Keep walking forward for about ten (10) more
                steps. Room two six seven (267) is at the end of this corridor, to the left passed a
                narrow open doorway.</string>

    <string name="end_point">You have arrived to room two six seven (267) which has its door to your
                left.</string>

    <string name="start_point">Please start walking forward for about twenty five (25) steps. Then turn
                cautiously to the left and take the sub-level stairways containing four steps
                down towards the main corridor.</string>

    <string name="response_yes">Your response was yes.</string>

    <string name="response_no">Your response was no.</string>

    <string name="yes_or_no">Please say yes or no only.</string>

    <string name="repeat">Would you like me to repeat?</string>

    <string name="please_repeat">Sorry I did not quite catch that. Please repeat your answer as yes
                or no only</string>


</resources>
