<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NaviBlind BLE GeoFence</string>
    <string name="floor_plan">Floor Plan</string>
    <string name="debug">BLE Scan</string>
    <string name="test">Test Activity</string>
    <string name="test_speech">Test Speech</string>
    <string name="text_to_speech">Text to Speech</string>


    <string name="empty"></string>

    <string name="no_service">Please wait...service not ready.</string>

    <string name="try_again">Please try again...say yes go on</string>

    <string name="welcome">NOT USED: Welcome to the Department of Computer Science. You are now
                on the second floor of the extension building.For room number two six
                seven, walk to your right towards the main door, this is normally open
                but please exercise caution.</string>

    <string name="welcome_two">You have now entered the second floor of the Computer Science Department.
                When ready to go, wait for the notification alert and say "yes go on".</string>

    <string name="main_door">This waypoint is NEAR LIFTS and STAIRS B: Please start walking forward for about
                fifteen (15) steps. Then turn cautiously to the right and take the sub-level stairways
                containing four steps down towards the main corridor.</string>

    <string name="after_main_door">NOT USED: Keep walking forward for about ten (10) steps. Then turn
                cautiously to the right and take the sub-level stairways containing four steps
                down towards the main corridor.</string>

    <string name="four_steps">Please be careful , confirm the presence of the four step sub-level stairway
                when you get there. When ready, please wait for the notification alert
                and say "yes go on".</string>

    <string name="narrow_corridor">This waypoint is FOUR STEPS and TOILETS: Be careful , use the hand rails and take the four
                step sub-level stairway down to the main corridor. This corridor is narrow and long, keep
                walking forward for about twenty five more (25) steps. At the end of this corridor take the
                sub-level stairways containing two steps up and turn to the right towards room number two six seven (267).
                </string>

    <string name="two_steps">Confirm the presence of the two step sub-level stairway
                when you get there. When ready, please wait for the notification alert
                and say "yes go on".</string>

    <string name="at_two_steps">This waypoint is TWO STEPS and STAIRS D: Use the hand rails and take the sub-level stairways containing
                two steps up and turn to the right towards room number two six seven (267). Keep walking forward for
                about fifteen (15) more steps. Room number two six seven (267) is at the end of this corridor,
                to the left passed a narrow open doorway.</string>

    <string name="end_point">This waypoint is ROOM 267: You have arrived to room number two six seven (267)
                which has its door in front of you.</string>

    <string name="narrow_open_doorway">Confirm the presence of the narrow open doorway
                when you get there. When ready, please wait for the notification alert
                and say "yes go on".</string>

    <string name="start_point">This waypoint is STAIRS E: Please start walking forward for about
                twenty five (25) steps. Then turn cautiously to the left and take the sub-level stairways
                containing four steps down towards the main corridor.</string>

    <string name="response_yes">Your response was yes.</string>

    <string name="response_no">Your response was no.</string>

    <string name="yes_or_no">Please say yes or no only.</string>

    <string name="repeat">Would you like me to repeat?</string>

    <string name="please_repeat">Please repeat your answer.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_text_to_speech">TextToSpeech</string>


</resources>
